A Guide to the Memorial Foundation for Children Records, 1811-2006 (bulk 1926-1999)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Administrative records, 1811-2005 (bulk 1890-1975), 7.9 cu. ft. (22 boxes); Boxes 22-41
  - Minutes, 1935-1937 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1938-1940 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1942-1945 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1948-1950 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1952-1956 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1965-1968 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1987-1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, Community Council, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, Nd (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Mission statements, 1957-1966 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Official permits, 1950-1970 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Organizational chart, nd (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Payroll, 1964-1968 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Personnel and Procedural Survey, 1954, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Pimlico Race Train and Preckness Train, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Press release, nd (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings of the 11th Year of Nemours Foundation Conferences on Crippled Children, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Property and building expenses, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Property and building expenses, 1956-1972 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Report on Audit, 1931-1937 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Report on Audit, 1938-1941 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Report on Examination, 1964, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Report of Superintendent, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, Nd (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. Elaine Rothenberg Study, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Rules for Children, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Staff directories, 1945, 1965, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - State Corporation Commission, Annual reports, 1965-1995 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Statement of Account from State-Planters Bank and Trust Company, 1931-1934 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Statement of Account from State-Planters Bank and Trust Company, 1935-1941 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Student work experience grant, 1964-1967 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Studies, Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Taxes, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Taxes, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Commodity Distribution Program, 1959-1964 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Virginia State Board of Charities Report, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Ways and Means, 1962-1964 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Lettie Pate Whitehead Foundation, 1959-1970 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook, 1920-1947 (Box 34)
  - Index cards (Box 35)
  - Photographs, Album, Part 1 of 3, c. 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Album, Part 2 of 3 c. 1960 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Album, Part 3 of 3 c. 1960 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Birthday, c. 1965 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Buildings, c. 1925-1940 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Buildings, Guidance Clinic, c. 1940 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Buildings, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 6a)
  - Photographs, Children, Identified, c. 1964-1966 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Children, Identified, c. 1964-1966 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Children, Identified, c. 1964-1966 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Children, Unidentified, c. 1940-1960 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Children at play, c. 1965 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Christmas, c. 1940 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, Christmas, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Christmas, c. 1965 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Christmas, c. 2000 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Easter, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Elk Hill Farm, c. 1970 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Groups, c. 1920 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Groups, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Groups, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Group of girls in front of school, c. 1930-1940 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Ms. Holt and Ms. McVeill, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Piano teacher, c. 1940 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Teacher and children, c. 1965 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, Teacher, Unidentified, c. 1965 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, Winter group and new bus, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, Negatives and slides, c. 1950-1990 (Box 38)
  - Photographs, Albums, c. 1958-1960 (Box 39)
  - Photographs, Oversize, c. 1900-1920 (Folder 59)
  - Wood block printing plates, Children and Pimlico races, c. 1960-1965 (Box 40)
  - Miscellaneous records (CLOSED UNTIL 2046) (Box 41)
- Series III: Case Files, 1891-1957, 8.2 cu. ft. (34 boxes); Boxes 42-74.
  - Case files, 1891-1923 (OPEN 1966-1998) (Box 42)
  - Case files, 1926 (OPEN 2001) (Box 43)
  - Case files, 1927 (OPEN 2002) (Box 44)
  - Case files, 1928 (OPEN 2003) (Box 45)
  - Case files, 1929 (OPEN 2004) (Box 46)
  - Case files, 1930 (OPEN 2005) (Box 47)
  - Case files, 1931 (OPEN 2006) (Box 48)
  - Case files, 1932 (OPEN 2007) (Box 49)
  - Case files, 1933 (OPEN 2008) (Box 50)
  - Case files, 1934 (OPEN 2009) (Box 51)
  - Case files, 1935 (OPEN 2010) (Box 52)
  - Case files, 1936 (CLOSED UNTIL 2011) (Box 53)
  - Case files, 1937 (CLOSED UNTIL 2012) (Box 54)
  - Case files, 1938 (CLOSED UNTIL 2013) (Box 55)
  - Case files, 1939 (CLOSED UNTIL 2014) (Box 56)
  - Case files, 1939 (CLOSED UNTIL 2014) (Box 57)
  - Case files, 1940 (CLOSED UNTIL 2015) (Box 58)
  - Case files, 1941 (CLOSED UNTIL 2016) (Box 59)
  - Case files, 1942 (CLOSED UNTIL 2017) (Box 60)
  - Case files, 1943 (CLOSED UNTIL 2018) (Box 61)
  - Case files, 1943 (CLOSED UNTIL 2018) (Box 62)
  - Case files, 1944 (CLOSED UNTIL 2019) (Box 63)
  - Case files, 1945 (CLOSED UNTIL 2020) (Box 64)
  - Case files, 1946 (CLOSED UNTIL 2021) (Box 65)
  - Case files, 1946 (CLOSED UNTIL 2021) (Box 66)
  - Case files, 1947 (CLOSED UNTIL 2022) (Box 67)
  - Case files, 1948 (CLOSED UNTIL 2023) (Box 68)
  - Case files, 1949-1952 (CLOSED UNTIL 2024-2027) (Box 69)
  - Case files, 1954 (CLOSED UNTIL 2029) (Box 70)
  - Case files, 1955 (CLOSED UNTIL 2030) (Box 71)
  - Case files, 1956 (CLOSED UNTIL 2031) (Box 72)
  - Case files, 1957 (CLOSED UNTIL 2032) (Box 73)
  - Scrapbook 1932 (CLOSED UNTIL 2007) (Box 74)